JENNIFER PRIDEMORE

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING LEAD AT ZIPLINE

+1 240 409 3070 | JennPride08@gmail.com | www.JennPridemore.com

MY GOALS

I aspire to make a positive impact on the world through my career, utilizing both my knowledge of technology and business to make a difference.

AT A GLANCE

I've built full stack production applications since 2013, with an emphasis on web and mobile design. I've lead several teams on dozens of initiatives, all while still acting as a key contributor to the code. Since 2012, I've worked at 5 different startups varying in size from 7 – 1000+ employees, and am always seeking to make a large impact in my role.

SKILLS

HTML Photoshop

CSS Illustrator

Git Procreate

Excel Google Analytics

WordPress Google AdWords

LANGUAGES

SPANISH	
JAVA	
JAVASCRIPT	
SWIFT	
PHP	
SQL	
NoSQL	
GIT	
PYTHON	

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING LEAD

(August 2021 – Present)

Zipline

- Leading a growing team of engineers in the development of solutions for ordering, inventory, and shipping
- Regularly developing full stack features and bug fixes as well as leading large scale migrations to green field applications
- Creating and communicating my team's roadmap and long term vision to the entire organization and external stakeholders

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER (Dec 2018 – July

2021)

Storvblocks

- Actively leading, managing, and on-boarding engineers at all levels with a focus on mentorship
- Lead a team of engineers in the creation of an audio review process, built out in a brand new Typescript application using Redux and Tailwind.
- Worked on projects including the removal of customer offering, a Redux dashboard accessing, watermarking and encoding audio content using FFMPEG, and backfilling of over 20 million pieces of content from 4 different sources into a single improved MongoDB instance

FOUNDING FRONT END ENGINEER (Oct 2017 – Oct 2018)

Agnes.io

- One of two frontend engineers to build out the Agnes mobile application in Ionic and AngularJS
- Lead the development in Agnes' web offering in React

EDUCATION

DUAL BACHELOR OF SCIENCE DEGREE

(August 2012 - May 2016)

University of Maryland, College Park Robert H. Smith School of Business Graduated with a double degree in Information Systems and Marketing, and a minor in Spanish.

INTERESTS







